Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XXIX: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
  - Men & Films - press releases, 1982-1983; cuid6774 (Box 174, Folder 57)
  - Men & Films - porn write-ups, Undated; cuid6775 (Box 174, Folder 58)
  - "Men of Manhattah" VHS cover, Undated; cuid6776 (Box 174, Folder 59)
  - Michael's Things, 1975; cuid6777 (Box 174, Folder 60)
  - Mid-Atlantic Leather, 2000; cuid6778 (Box 174, Folder 61)
  - Mission Statement - Archives project, Undated; cuid6779 (Box 174, Folder 62)
  - NYC Comptroller Commendation, 1992; cuid6780 (Box 174, Folder 63)
  - NYC Pride Guide, 2005; cuid6781 (Box 174, Folder 64)
  - New York Magazine - with pieces of Calvin Klein article cut out, 1995; cuid6782 (Box 174, Folder 65)
  - New York Times - "Supreme Court Roundup", Undated; cuid6783 (Box 174, Folder 66)
  - News Clippings - Woodstock, Undated; cuid6784 (Box 174, Folder 67)
  - Next, #13.21, 2005; cuid6785 (Box 174, Folder 68)
  - Non-Profit Startup - CRE, Undated; cuid6786 (Box 174, Folder 69)
  - Notes and fragments, Undated; cuid6787 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Nova TBC - warranty and manual, Undated; cuid6788 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Nude pictures, Undated; cuid6789 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Out on Wednesday, 1994; cuid6790 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Paper Magazine, 1997; cuid6791 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Party Journal, Undated; cuid6792 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Passport paper and envelope selector, Undated; cuid6793 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Petrified Film, Inc. - stock footage list, Undated; cuid6794 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Phillip Morris [sponsorship], Undated; cuid6795 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Phillip Morris sponsorship proposal for 1992 Presidential campaign coverage, 1991; cuid6796 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - "Photo File" - magazine and newspaper clippings, Undated; cuid6797 (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - Photos (paper prints) of demonstrations and politicians, Undated; cuid6798 (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - Press coverage of GCN shows, Undated; cuid6799 (Box 175, Folder 13)
  - Press Pass info, 1999; cuid6800 (Box 175, Folder 14)
  - Press Passes, 1984; 1988; cuid6801 (Box 175, Folder 15)
  - Pride Channel Network - business plan, 1995; cuid6802 (Box 175, Folder 16)
  - Production lists, Undated; cuid6803 (Box 175, Folder 17)
  - Program catalog, 1982; cuid6804 (Box 175, Folder 18)
  - Program catalogs - Men & Films, Pride & Progress, Right Stuff, 1982; cuid6805 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Program lists, Undated; cuid6806 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Public Access Television Policy and Procedure Guide, 1993; cuid6807 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations, 1989; cuid6808 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - P.R. Masters, Undated; cuid6809 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Recent Applicants, Undated; cuid6810 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Release Forms, Undated; cuid6811 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Ringling Bros. & Barnum and Bailey - presented by Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc., 1983; cuid6812 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - "A Special Opportunity for First Time Advertisers", Undated; cuid6813 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Staff Training; Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies, CUNY, Undated; cuid6814 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Stallion, 1982; cuid6815 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Tape Inventory, Undated; cuid6816 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - "Television Operational Measurements", Undated; cuid6817 (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Top Man, 1980; cuid6818 (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Top Man - Men & Films, 1982; cuid6819 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - Tucson Women's Video Festival flyer, 1984; cuid6820 (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - Vacu-tech - brochure original, Undated; cuid6821 (Box 176, Folder 17)
  - Verizon bill, 2007; cuid6822 (Box 176, Folder 18)
  - "Video" chapter in unidentified book, Undated; cuid6823 (Box 176, Folder 19)
  - Video course, Undated; cuid6824 (Box 176, Folder 20)
  - Video description and cover - "Slave's Revenge", "Rural Raunch", Undated; cuid6825 (Box 176, Folder 21)
  - Video list, Undated; cuid6826 (Box 176, Folder 22)
  - Videomaster's Preliminary Production Checklist (FACL), 1981; cuid6827 (Box 176, Folder 23)
  - The Village Voice - "The Cable Rednecks", 1983; cuid6828 (Box 176, Folder 24)
  - "Whoop-Dee-Doo" - magazine and newspaper clippings, Undated; cuid6829 (Box 176, Folder 25)
  - Woodstock Access TV Times, 1983; cuid6830 (Box 176, Folder 26)
- Oversize Series XXIX: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
  This series contains the oversize paper materials from the Lou Maletta and GCN files series.
  - Subseries A: Files
    - 32 Union Sq. East - address cards - originals, Undated; cuid6831 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - The Advocate - "Gay TV on Yasgur's Farm" - mounted article, issue 363, Undated; cuid6832 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Arcos Blancos: San Juan's Premiere Guest House - print, Undated; cuid6833 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - The Assembly, State of NY Citation for Lou Maletta as an Outstanding Citizen, 1992; cuid6834 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - DARE newsletter - vol.1, no. 27, 1988; cuid6835 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Donna Summer - "She Works Hard for the Money" full page ad - Billboard, 1983; cuid6836 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - FACIT - letterhead original, Undated; cuid6837 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - "Gay Cable Network Day" proclamation, 1991; cuid6838 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Gay USA - Achievement Award from ICAN - "Best Network Original Program", 1991; cuid6839 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - GCN 10th Anniversary Gala invitation, 1992; cuid6840 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - GCN Conventions '88 - flyer originals, Undated; cuid6841 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - GCN - letterhead originals, Undated; cuid6842 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - GCN / Lou Maletta business cards - original, Undated; cuid6843 (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - GCN - party invitation master, Undated; cuid6844 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Hong Kong Men - 1996 Calendar, cuid6845 (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - "Le Gai Pied" poster, Undated; cuid6846 (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Logo design boards, Undated; cuid6847 (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Louis P. Maletta - letterhead original, Undated; cuid6848 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Lou Maletta Photography - logo original, Undated; cuid6849 (Box 177, Folder 19)
    - Luke P. Valenti - letterhead original, Undated; cuid6850 (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - Men & Films - business cards original, Undated; cuid6851 (Box 177, Folder 21)
    - Men & Films - flyer originals, Undated; cuid6852 (Box 177, Folder 22)
    - Men & Films - letterhead original, Undated; cuid6853 (Box 177, Folder 23)
    - Men & Films - promo print, Undated; cuid6854 (Box 177, Folder 24)
    - Men of Manhattan - mailers original, Undated; cuid6855 (Box 177, Folder 25)
    - Model release form - original, Undated; cuid6856 (Box 177, Folder 26)
    - "The Monster" poster - original, Undated; cuid6857 (Box 177, Folder 27)
    - Night of a Thousand Gowns - videotape cover original, 1987; cuid6858 (Box 177, Folder 28)
    - Note from Emma, Undated; cuid6859 (Box 177, Folder 29)
    - NY Attorney General letter of support, 1992; cuid6860 (Box 177, Folder 30)
    - "NYPD is Hiring" poster, 1996; cuid6861 (Folder 13 Right)
    - Photograph - portrait of Lou Maletta, 1987; cuid6862 (Box 177, Folder 31)
    - Photographs - protest in the U.K., 1988; cuid6863 (Box 177, Folder 32)
    - "Power, Presence and Purpose" - photocopied article, Undated; cuid6864 (Box 177, Folder 33)
    - Rate cards - originals, Undated; cuid6865 (Box 177, Folder 34)
    - State of NY Executive Chamber citation, 1992; cuid6866 (Box 177, Folder 35)
    - Videotape order form - original, Undated; cuid6867 (Box 177, Folder 36)
  - Subseries B: Periodicals
    - The Advocate, no. 361, 364, 1983; cuid6868 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - The Connections - vol. 2, no. 7, 8, 11, 1983; cuid6869 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - The Connection - vol. 2, no. 22, 1983; cuid6870 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - The Dallas Downtown News - vol. 7, no. 44, 1984; cuid6871 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - The Dallas Morning News - Convention '84, 1984; cuid6872 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Dallas Voice - vol. 1, no. 15, 1984; cuid6873 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Dollars & Sense - vol. 13, no. 8, 1982; cuid6874 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Life Magazine, 1971; cuid6875 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - The Medical Herald - vol. 17, no. 11, 2005; cuid6876 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Mixed newspaper clippings, 1978; 1983-1984; cuid6877 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Multichannel News - vol. 5, no. 50, 1984; cuid6878 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - New York Blade, 2002-2003; cuid6879 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - New York Blade, 2003-2004; cuid6880 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - The New York City News, 1983; cuid6881 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - The National Law Journal, 1985; cuid6882 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - New York Press - vol. 17, no. 39, 2004; cuid6883 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - San Jose Mercury News - convention edition, 1984; cuid6884 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - The Spiritual Herald - vol. 4, no. 11, 2005; cuid6885 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Stonewall News - no. 72, 1994; cuid6886 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Sunday Record, 1983; cuid6887 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - The Vault, 1995; cuid6888 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - The Village Voice, 1983; 2008; cuid6889 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - The Weekly News, 1986; cuid6890 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Wire, no. 20, 1995; cuid6891 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - The Woodstock Times - vol. 12, no. 8, 9, 10, 1983; cuid6892 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - The Woodstock Times - vol. 12, no. 13, 15, 1983; cuid6893 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Ulster County Townsman - vol. XXX, no. 8-10, 14, 1983; cuid6894 (Box 179, Folder 13)
- Series XXX: Photographs
  This series contains all of the photographs, slides, and negatives from the GCN files.
  - Mixed photographs, including GCN staff, protests, and pornography., Undated; cuid6895 (Binder A)
- Series XXXI: Objects
  This series contains objects kept by Lou Maletta and GCN.
  - Purple T-shirt with GCN logo on back, Undated; cuid6896 (Box 181, Object ID: 231.2.0003)
  - Purple T-shirt with GCN logo on front, Undated; cuid6897 (Box 181, Object ID: 231.2.0004)
    There are two copies of this shirt, one of which has had the sleeves cut off.
  - Tye-dye T-shirt from Conventions '88 with several GCN logos, 1988; cuid6898 (Box 182, Object ID: 231.2.0005)
    There are six copies of this shirt, one of which has had the collar cut off.
- Oversize Series XXXI: Objects
  - GCN TV license plate, Undated; cuid6899 (Box 180, Item ID: 231.2.0006)
  - GCN plaque, Undated; cuid6900 (Box 180, Item ID: 231.2.0007)
  - GLAAD Media Award to Gay Cable Network, 1990; cuid6901 (Box 180, Item ID: 231.2.0008)
  - Leather New York Weekweed salute plaque for Lou Maletta, 1993; cuid6902 (Box 180, Item ID: 231.2.0009)
  - Life Achievement Award from VBL-NYC to Gay Cable Network, 1986; cuid6903 (Box 180, Item ID: 231.2.0010)
  - Marble plaque - "Accept Differences, Be Kind...", 2003; cuid6904 (Box 180, Object ID: 231.2.0001)
  - Press Passes, 1984-1997; cuid6905 (Box 180, Item ID: 231.2.0011)
  - Wooden camera with "GCN" on front, Undated; cuid6906 (Box 180, Object ID: 231.2.0002)